Guide to the African Collection, Yale University Library, Records of the Curator
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1965-1990; Accession 1998-A-127
  - South African Information Exchange Working Paper Series, 1993–1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - South African Institute of International Affairs, 1985–1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - South African Institute for Public Administration, 1980–1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - South Africa Iron, Steel, and Allied Industries Union, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - South Africa Jewish Board of Deputies, 1969–1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - South African Labour Bulletin, 1990–1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - South African Labour Education Project, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - South Africa University Bureau of Market Research (UNISA), 1973–1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - South African Political Studies Association, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - South African Society for Quaternary Research (SASQUA), 1980–1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - South African Society of Archivists, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - South West Africa Scientific Society (Windhoek), 1972–1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - South African Economist, 1991–1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Southern Africa Information Services, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - South African Research Program, 1992–1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - South African Communication Service, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Southern African Update, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - South African Historical Society, 1987–1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - South African Library, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - South African Library, 1990–1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - South African Library, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - South African Museum of Military History, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - South African Tourism Board, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Southern African Catholic Bishops' Conference, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Southern African Forum, 1984–1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Southern African Information Exchange, 1991–1995 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Southern African Research Association, 1976–1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Southern African Review of Books, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Southern African Rock Art Research Association (SARARA), 1987 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Southern African Society for Quaternary Research, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - South African Society for Cultural History, 1986–1998 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Southern African Political Economy Series, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Southern Africa Report, 1983–1997 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - South African Society of Archivists, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - University of South Africa, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Suid-Afrikaanse Institut, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Spain, 1967–1985 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Sudan, 1965–1984 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Switzerland, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Tanzania, 1970–1979 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Tanganyika - Tanzania, 1963–1969 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Togo, 1964–1982 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Transkei, 1969–1979 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Transvaal, 1968–1988 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Tristan da Cunha (and dependents), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Tunisia, 1968–1980 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Uganda, 1965–1986 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - USSR Embassy, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - United States A. I. D., 1972–1982 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - United States Air Force, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - United States Congress, 1969–1980 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - United States Congress, 1982–1986 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - United States Consulates, 1973–1978 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - United States Department of the Army AG Publications Center, 1977–1983 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - United States Department of Defense, 1984–1989 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - United States Department of Education, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - United States Department of the Navy, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - United States Department of State, 1973–1987 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - United States Embassies, 1971–1987 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - United States National Archives, 1965–1971 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - United States Peace Corps, 1978–1980 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous United States government departments, 1970–1987 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Upper Volta, 1969–1975 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Zaire, 1974–1980 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Zimbabwe Information Office, 1970–1983 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Big Game Hunting, 1980–1992 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Big Game Hunting - Kenya, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - World Wide Hunting Books, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Price list of AFC publications, Undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Yale University Press books available on exchange (Africa), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Southern African Research, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - National bibliographies, 1967–1977 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Dahomey (selected bibliography), Undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Dauphin list, Undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Institut de Recherches Scientifiques du Cameroun - Yaounde, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Linguistics bibliography - Case Memorial Library, Hartford Seminary Foundation, Hartford, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Perrot lists, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Ibadan names, Undated (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Desiderata: North-East Africa (Jones), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Publishers list, 1966–1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - South Africa official publications lists
    - 1986–1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1984–1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1982–1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1980–1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1978–1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1974–1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1971–1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1968–1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1965–1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 1961–1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - South Africa periodicals, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Uganda bibliography (Makerere University Library), 1963–1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Colonel Henry A. Siegel Anglers' & Shooters Bookshelf, 1992–1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Antiquarian Books Indian Ocean & Bowman, Larry W. "Bookseller", 1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Argo Publications - invoices, 1995 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Argo Publications correspondence, 1994 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Arquivo Historico de Mocambique, 1982–1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Atere-Roberts, D. N., 1990–1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Atere-Roberts, D. B. (Davidson), 1990–1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Atrium Bookshop Mrs. Maureen Hargraves, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Biblarte, Limitada Antiquarian Booksellers, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Boer War book, 1994–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Boer War books, 1990–1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Boer War books, 1988–1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - R. R. Bowker - invoices, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Bowker Saur, 1991–1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Brenthurst Press, 1981–1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - David Brooks, 1990–1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Bullfrog Films, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Butterworths, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Clarke's Bookshop correspondence, 1991 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Clarke's Bookshop invoices, 1994 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Clarke's Bookshop correspondence, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Codesria Publications Dakar, Senegal, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Cup Services, 1990–1992 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Dar Mahjar invoices, 1990 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Dar Mahjar correspondence, 1990 January–1991 December (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Dar Mahjar invoices, 1989 January–1989 July (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Datafilm (Pty) Limited - Mr. John Outhwaite, 1990–1992 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Datamics, Incorporated micropublishers, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Exclusive Books invoices, 1989–1990 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Fash-Enterprise Books invoices, 1991 January–1991 December (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Garvey-Tubman-Nanny-Nzinga Press, 1994–1995 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Hogarth Representation invoices, 1995 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Hogarth Representation correspondence, 1994 January–1995 December (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Holleyman & Treacher Limited, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Deheer, A. N., 1990–1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Dillons Bookstore invoices, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - D'Souza, John A., 1992 January–1995 December (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mark Duffill correspondence, 1991 January–1994 December (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Emerald Isle Books, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - E. M. Lawson & Company, 1993–1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Exclusive Books correspondence file, 1989–1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Exclusive Books invoices, 1991 January–1991 December (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Leishman & Taussig invoices and correspondence, 1991 December–1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Leishman & Taussig correspondence, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Leishman & Taussig invoices, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - McBlain Books, 1992–1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - McBlain Books, 1990–1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - McRae, Michael T., 1984–1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Microfile Limited, Johannesburg invoices, 1991 January–1993 December (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Microfile Limited, Johannesburg invoices, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Microform Limited, 1977–1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Micrographics - invoices, 1988–1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Micrographics - correspondence, 1988–1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Nicholas Morrell Rare Books Limited, 1986–1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - University of Natal Press, 1988–1989 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Nigerian Book Suppliers invoices, 1991 January–1992 December (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Nigerian Book Suppliers correspondence, 1991 January–1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Nigerian Book Suppliers invoices, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Nigerian Book Suppliers correspondence, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Okike, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Simon Ottenberg, Bookseller, 1991 January–1991 December (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Photographic Images International correspondence, 1989–1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Reed Reference Publishing, 1994–1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Ross, Norman Publishing Incorporated invoices, 1989 January–1993 December (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Ross, Norman Publishing Company correspondence, 1987 January–1989 December (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Ross, Norman Publishing Incorporated correspondence, 1990 January–1993 December (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Safari Press - Ludo J. Wurfbain, 1992–1993 December (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Sawyer, 1965–1995 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Sawyer Bookseller invoices, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Tempo Grafcia, S. A. R. L., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Terrorism Research in association with Research Associates, 1989–1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Thorold, Frank R.
    - Correspondence, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Invoices, 1995 January–1995 December (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1995 January–1995 December (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Invoices, 1994 January–1994 December (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1994 January–1994 December (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Invoices, 1993 January–1993 December (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 January–1993 December (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1991 January–1991 December (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - General, 1991 January–1992 December (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Invoices, 1990 January–1990 December (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Trophy room books, 1993 January–1993 December (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Trophy room books, 1992 August–1992 December (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - University Microfilms International Invoices, 1990–1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - University Microfilms International Dissertations Catalogues & Lists, 1970–1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - University Place Bookshop Invoices & Correspondence, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - University Bookshop Invoices (Ghana), 1989–1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - J.L. van Schaik (PTY) LTD Pretoria "Invoices", 1989–1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Africanist Organizations, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Anti-Apartheid Groups, Parties, 1978–1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Archives, 1980 April (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Associations & Societies A-Z, 1964–1986 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous authors, 1964–1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Banks, 1965–1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Catholic Church, 1982–1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Chambers of Commerce & Industry, 1964–1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Charitable/Relief Organizations, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Church Organizations, 1985–1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Colleges, Universities, Schools, Centers & Institutes, 1968–1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Conference File, 1964–1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - I.A.I. Bibliog Conference Nairobi, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Copyright, 1983–1987 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Corporations II, 1974–1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Corporations I, 1964–1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (individuals to AFC requiring information, etc.), 1971–1988 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Demographers, 1965–1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Employee Participation Meetings, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Engineering Firms, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Inquiries on Estates, etc., 1969–1973 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous foundations, 1971–1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Historical Societies (A-Z), 1968–1977 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Jewish Organizations, 1982–1986 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Municipal, County & Provincial Libraries and Record Offices & Miscellaneous Libraries, 1967–1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - MAP & other visual aids, circa 1980s (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Medicine, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Microfilms, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Microform Information Sheet, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Military journals, 1970–1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Missionary Societies & Miscellaneous Religious Bodies, 1967–1977 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Municipalities II, 1977–1987 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Municipalities I, 1963–1976 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Museum & Art Galleries, 1961–1985 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Hogarth Representatives Corres., 1996 January–1996 December (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Holsten, Theodore J. Jr., 1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - W. Lable, 1977–1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Livraria Portugal Dias & Andrade, LDA, 1994–1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Microfile Ltd, Johannesburg Invoices & Correspondence, 1995 January–1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Reuben Musiker, 1972–1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Refugee Voices, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Revue D'Histoire Maghrebine, 1990–1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ross, Norman Publishing Inc., 1994 January–1996 December (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Safari Press - Ludo J. Wurfbain, 1994 January–1997 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Third World Publications, 1975–1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Thorold's Frank R. Invoices, 1998 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Thorold's Frank R. Invoices, 1996 January–1997 December (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Trophy room books, 1995 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Wheldon & Wesley Ltd., 1994–1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - ABC-TV (Television), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Abraham, Isabel Mrs., 1993 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Acson Communications Limited, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Addressee, 1994 May 27 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Adcock, Catherine L., 1989–1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Aberdeen University, 1974 February 6–1975 April 7 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - African-American Labor Center, 1981 September 24 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - African Association for Public Administration and Management, 1972 December 28–1973 January 5 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - African Institute of South Africa Pretoria, South Africa, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - African Journal of Political Science, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - African Literature Association, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - African Studies Associates Emory University, 1994 February 17–1995 December 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - African Studies Association, 1996–1998 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - African Studies Association Spring Meeting, 1992–1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - African Studies Centre, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Afropaedia, L.L.C., 1997–1998 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Afro-American Research Center, Inc., 1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Algemeen Rijksarchief Te (Netherlands), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Altair Publishing, 1993 January–1994 January 21 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Amax Inc., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Ambrose, David, 1990–1998 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - American Council of Voluntary Agencies for Foreign Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - American Freedom from Hunger Foundation, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - The American Journal of Science, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - American Library Association-Chicago, 1973–1990 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - American Library Association-New York, 1980–1981 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - American Library Association, Resources & Technical Services Division., Catalog Code Committee, 1975–1978 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - American Library Association-Houston Conference, 1977 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - American Society of African Culture, 1965–1966 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - American Universities Field Staff, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - American University. Beirut, Cairo, D.C., etc, 1979–1982 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Americans Against Apartheid, 1986–1987 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Amherst College, 1963–1967 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Amistad Research Center, 1983–1997 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - ANC, Department of Information & Publicity, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Andrew Levy & Associates (Pty) Ltd, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Anitepam, 1995 June 7 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Anglo American Corporation of South Africa Limited, 1986–1993 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - A.P.I. Study D'Italianistica Nell' Africa Australe Italian Studies in Southern Africa, 1990–1996 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Arab Historical Review for Ottoman Studies, 1991 January–1991 December (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - CODESA Documents, 1992 April 21 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Anti-Apartheids Beweging Nederland, 1981 June 12 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement, 1994 October 13 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Anti-Censorship Action Group, 1994 January 6 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Antwerp University, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Archives Guides, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - University of Arizona, 1974–1994 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Armagh, North Ireland Public Library Provincial Registry, 1968–1969 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - African Studies Association Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Arnold Bergstraesser Institut, 1988–1989 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Art Libraries Society of North America, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Askins, G.J. Bookseller, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Asmara University, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Association of African Studies Programs, 1972–1982 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Association of Caribbean Studies, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Association for French Studies in Southern Africa, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Association for the Study of Afro-American Life and History, 1968–1978 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Association Historique Internationale De L'Ocean Indien, 1982 June 25 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Association Internationale De La Securite Sociale, 1980 January 31 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Association of African Universities-Accra, Ghana, 1972–1981 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Association of Concerned Africa Scholars, 1981–1997 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Association of Research Libraries, 1993–1996 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Atlanta University, 1968–1978 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Australian Council for Overseas Aid, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Australian National University, 1977–1982 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Awosola, Owolabi, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - The Azania Labour Journal, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Bahia Universidade Federal, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Baker, Donald Professor Long Island University, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Book Refunds, 1980–1989 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Travellers CK Advances, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Ademulegun, Olu, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Africana Book Collectors-Pretoria, 1973–1980 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - African Books Collective (ABC), 1991 January–1992 December (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - African Books Collective (ABC), 1991–1997 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - African Imprint-Invoices, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - African Imprint Library Services Correspondence, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Ambrose, David-Invoices, 1997 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Ambrose, David-Correspondence, 1997 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Ambrose, David-Invoices, 1987–1997 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Apfelbaum, Charles, 1990–1997 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - ARGO Publicatoin-Invoices, 1997–1998 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - ARGO Publications Correspondence, 1997 January–1998 December (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - ARGO Publications-Invoices, 1996 January–1996 December (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - ARGO Publications Correspondence, 1996 January–1996 December (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - BAHRI SONS-Book Sellers&Stationery, 1990–1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Boer War Books, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - California Newsreel, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Clarke's Bookshop "Invoices", 1996 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Clarke's Bookshop correspondence, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Dar Mahjar "Invoices", 1996 January–1997 December (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - D'Souza, John, 1996 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Duffill, Mark-correspondence, 1997 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mark Duffill Invoices, 1997 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mark Duffill-Correspondence, 1995 January–1996 December (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mark Duffill Invoices, 1995 January–1996 December (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - First Run/Icarus Films, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Gamble, David P., 1997 May 19 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Great Epic Books, 1996 October 25 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hogarth Representation Invoices, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hogarth Representives Corresp., 1997 January–1998 December (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Hogarth Representatives Invoices, 1997 January–1997 December (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hogarth Representatives Invoices, 1996 January–1996 December (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Ballarat College of Advanced Education, 1985 October 22 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Mrs. Joan Banks, 1990–1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Bareiss, Hugh McB., 1997 April 28 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Basel Mission, 1991 December (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Basler Africa Bibliographien, 1991–1997 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Bath University, 1982 July 20 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Batten, A.G.M., 1977–1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Bayero University, 1980–1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Bayreuth Universitat, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Belfast Library, 1967–1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Belgisch Institutut voor Voorlichting en Documentatie, 1980 April 18 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Beloit College, 1983–1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Bemath, Abdul S., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Benin University Library, 1971–1993 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Bergen University, 1980–1983 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Bessant, Leslie, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Bhana's Mahomed S. Agency, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Bibliotheque Aequatoria Bamanya, 1994 June 29 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Bibliotheque Africaine, Brussels, 1981–1986 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris, 1981–1989 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Biersteker, Ann Professor, 1994 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Binghamton University, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - B.H. Blackwell Ltd., 1992–1994 (Box 14, Folder 41)